fcbanking.com 2010-11-20

# Privacy Policy

### FIRST COMMONWEALTH FINANCIAL CORPORATION ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY FOR CLIENTS

The First Commonwealth Financial Corporation (First Commonwealth) family of companies is committed to safeguarding the information you provide us and this commitment extends to online banking. While our **Privacy Policy for Clients** is the same whether you are online or not, we have extra privacy measures in place to protect your information when you bank online with us. The sections below describe these extra measures.

#### Cookies

First Commonwealth does not automatically collect personal information from visitors to its Web sites. Cookies are small pieces of information that a Web site stores on a visitor's Web browser. First Commonwealth uses cookies only in Internet Banking. Cookies are a requirement for this service so that we can protect the privacy of your transactions. However, we limit the use of cookies by establishing a new cookie for each Internet Banking session.

First Commonwealth does not store confidential or classified information in cookies. Cookies cannot be used to capture your e-mail address, gain confidential or classified information about you, or obtain data from the hard drive of your computer. Some Web sites use cookies to obtain information from your browser but cookies can only be read by the Web site that set the cookie. You can control the use of cookies by setting your browser to give you the opportunity of accepting or rejecting an incoming cookie.

#### Links to Non-First Commonwealth sites

First Commonwealth is not responsible for the information collection practices of the non-First Commonwealth links you click to from our Web pages. We cannot guarantee how these third parties use cookies or whether they place on your computer cookies that may identify you personally. First Commonwealth urges you to review the privacy policies of each of the linked Web sites you visit - before you provide them with any personally identifiable information.

### FIRST COMMONWEALTH FINANCIAL CORPORATION PRIVACY POLICY FOR CLIENTS

#### What you should know

We recognize our obligation to keep information about you secure and confidential. There is some important information we want you to know.

  1. Unlike many other financial institutions, we do not sell Client Information to marketers outside First Commonwealth who may want to offer you their own products and services.
  2. We do not control advertising (mail, telephone or e-mail) you receive from companies outside First Commonwealth. You can reduce outside advertising by contacting the Direct Marketing Association and the credit reporting bureaus and by registering on the do not call registry.
  3. We carefully manage information among our companies. Understanding your relationship with First Commonwealth allows us to serve you better and offer you more convenience and benefits.

This policy covers Client Information, which means personally identifiable information about a consumer or a consumer's current or former relationship with First Commonwealth, including the companies listed under the section First Commonwealth Companies.

This policy is provided to you annually as required by the Federal Financial Privacy Law.

If you previously exercised your option to limit the sharing of Client Information among First Commonwealth Companies, or limit marketing offers from First Commonwealth Companies, you don't need to take any additional action.

#### Protecting information about you from marketers outside First Commonwealth

First Commonwealth does not sell or otherwise share any Client Information with marketers outside of First Commonwealth who may want to offer you their own products and services. You do not need to take any action to prevent disclosure of this information.

#### Making the security of information a priority

Keeping financial information secure is one of our most important responsibilities. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect Client Information. Employees are authorized to access Client Information only when they have a reasonable business need for the information. Our employees are required to give confidential treatment to Client Information and are subject to disciplinary action if they fail to do so.

#### Collecting information

We collect and use various types of information to service your accounts, save you time and money, and better respond to your needs.

Client Information is categorized as the following four types:

  1. Application Information - information, such as your assets, income and debt, which you provide to us on applications and through other means.
  2. Transaction and Experience Information - information about your transactions and account experience, such as your account balances, payment history, and parties to transactions; or information about our communications with you, such as requests for copies of checks and our responses.
  3. Consumer Report Information - information from a consumer report, such as your creditworthiness or credit history.
  4. Information from Outside Sources - information from outside sources regarding their employment, credit and other relationships with you or verifying representations made by you, such as your employment history, loan balances and your property insurance.

#### Managing Information

We manage how and when information is shared:

  * Within First Commonwealth
  * With companies that work for us
  * In other situations

#### Managing Information within First Commonwealth

First Commonwealth is made up of a number of companies, including financial service providers such as our bank and our insurance agency. Please refer to the section First Commonwealth Companies for a list of our companies that may receive or share information about consumer client relationships.

First Commonwealth may share all four types of Client Information among our companies. For example, if you have an account with one of our companies and would like to open an account with another of our companies, we may share information you have provided to us. Sharing this information could save you time in opening your new account because you might not need to furnish the same information twice. Sharing information also enhances our ability to protect your accounts against fraudulent activity on an account. For example, we may use information about your ATM and debit card transactions to identify any unusual activity, and then contact you to determine if your card has been lost or stolen.

We occasionally receive medical or health information about a client if, for example, a client applies for insurance from us. We do not share medical or health information among our companies except to maintain accounts, process transactions, service client requests, or perform insurance functions.

#### Managing Information with companies that work for us

We may share any of the four types of Client Information outlined above with companies that work for us. All companies that act on our behalf are contractually obligated to keep the information we provide to them confidential, and use the Client Information that we share only to provide the services we ask them to perform for you and us. These companies may include financial service providers such as asset management companies, and nonfinancial companies such as check printing and data processing companies. These companies might assist us, for example, in fulfilling your service requests and processing your transactions. In addition, we may share any of the four types of Client Information with financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements.

#### Managing Information in other situations

We may also share any of the four types of Client Information to credit bureaus and similar organizations, and when required or permitted by law. For example, Client Information may be disclosed in connection with a subpoena or similar legal process, a fraud investigation, recording mortgages in public records, or the sale of your account to another financial institution. We may also share any of the four types of Client Information outside First Commonwealth if we have your consent, such as when we respond to your service requests.

#### Honoring your preferences

You have a choice when it comes to how First Commonwealth shares certain types of Client Information.

#### Sharing among First Commonwealth companies

Affiliate sharing: You may request that Application Information, Consumer Report Information and Information from Outside Sources not be shared among First Commonwealth companies. However, through the normal course of doing business, we will continue to share Transaction and Experience Information among our companies to service your accounts and better meet your financial needs.

Affiliate marketing: Federal law gives you the right to limit some but not all marketing offers from our family of First Commonwealth companies. Federal law also requires us to give you this notice to tell you about your choice to limit marketing from our affiliates. You may limit the First Commonwealth companies, such as the bank and insurance agency affiliates, from marketing their products and services to you if you do not have an account or business relationship with them. These marketing offers are based on your personal information that they receive from other First Commonwealth companies. This information includes your income, your account history, and your credit score. Your choice to limit marketing offers from the First Commonwealth companies will apply until you tell us to change your choice.

If you do not want First Commonwealth to share Application Information, Consumer Report Information and Information from Outside Sources among First Commonwealth companies, or you want First Commonwealth to limit marketing offers, you can tell us that by:

  1. Calling us toll-free at 1.888.711.2265 and using our Convenience Banking Line. You will need a touch-tone phone for this option.
  2. Calling us toll-free at 1.800.711.2265 and talking with a Convenience Banking Center representative.
  3. Talking to a client representative at your local community office or your client relationship manager.

Certain information will be requested in order to assure that your preference is honored across all your accounts.

To help you understand how we record your preference about sharing Client Information, you should know that:

  * Your preference will be honored among all First Commonwealth Companies
  * You may receive more than one copy of the Privacy Policy. However, once you have told us about your preference, it will remain in effect until you tell us to change it.
  * If you have joint accounts, we will treat a request by one party to the account as applying to all parties to the account. A preference will apply to accounts that each joint account holder has in his or her name and any accounts the joint account holders have with each other.
  * Since some marketing programs may already be in progress, it may take a short time for your preference to be fully effective.

#### Making sure information is accurate

Keeping your account information accurate and up to date is very important. We provide you with access to your account information through various means, such as account statements, Telephone Banking and Internet Banking. If your account information is incomplete, inaccurate or not current, please call or write us at the telephone number or address listed on your account statement, bank records, or other documentation. We will promptly update or correct any erroneous information. If you have questions or feel that we have not handled information about you properly, you may contact us and we will investigate your inquiry or complaint.

#### Keeping up-to-date with our Privacy Policy

First Commonwealth will provide notice of our Privacy Policy annually, as long as you maintain an ongoing relationship with us.

#### First Commonwealth Companies

The following is a list of the First Commonwealth companies that may receive or share Client Information:

  * Commonwealth Trust Credit Life Insurance Co.
  * First Commonwealth Bank
  * First Commonwealth Community Development Corporation
  * First Commonwealth Financial Advisors Inc.
  * First Commonwealth Financial Corporation
  * First Commonwealth Insurance Agency
  * First Commonwealth Home Mortgage 
  * FraMal Holdings Corporation
